The Pythonist
On the previous episode
Understanding History of Python
Before coding in Python is important.
Today, the Python language of everything, web development, data science, machine learning, automation, AI tools and chatbots.
Now on the next episode.
In the next episode, two first Python project, objectives are, understand what a variable is, something that stores information.
Stores Hello World in a variable called greeting.
Print it to the screen using print function.
Today I'm going to teach you how to write your first Python project, which is the first Python project at simple.
You store hello world into a variable and then you take that variable.
You put it into a function, a built-in function called print so that it can't display it to the screen.
So set back, relax, let's start typing.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, we're making easy, we're making easy.
Well, well, so we're on the right.
So well, yeah, I'm going to put myself up on the diet.
But finally, I'm banking on full-life money.
Living in hangars, what they fear it.
But finally, I'm selling them, they make money.
I'm going to put myself up on the diet.
But finally, I'm banking on full-life money.
Living in hangars, what they fear it.
But finally, I'm selling them, they make money.
What fear, fear, fear, what is a fear, fear, fear.
Right click and choose Open Integrated Terminal.
Type Python followed by the script name called HelloWorld.py.
Press Enter to run the script, it occured Hello World to the screen as shown in the tutorial.
Greeting Variable Stored Hello World.
Print function contained greeting variable.
Run Python followed by script name here the script name is HelloWorld.py.
Check online courses here at DataCamp.
There is Python, SQL, R, Power BI, Excel etc.